# YUNTING SHAO

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Arts, Media Art And Performance - Creative Technologies, 06/2023

University of Regina - Regina, SK

Raymond and Helen McDonald Prize, 2023 From Campion College at the PROFILES University of Regina

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Artistic Video editor with outstanding proficiency in Adobe Premiere Pro and Adobe Photoshop and multi-camera editing expertise in video productions and also creative design. Efficient and reliable with passion for bringing creative projects to duration. Reliable intern studying post - production seeks an internship opportunity to expand skills and gain valuable real - world experience to seek and maintain a position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, reliable with time management and problem - solving skills. A friendly graduated candidate is available for day - time, evening, weekends and holiday shifts. Considered hard working, punctual and driven. Detail - oriented, organized and meticulous employee. Works at fast pace to meet tight deadlines. Enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company success.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

## Automotive Detailer, 07/2023 - Current Enterprise Truck Rental, Regina, SK

- Vacuumed interiors of vehicles to remove dirt and debris.
- Maintained car detailing equipment and supplies in optimal condition for daily demands.
- Inspected interior and exterior of vehicles for cleanliness and accurately identified imperfections outside vehicle standards.
- Washed, waxed, and buffed vehicle bodies for professional shine.
- Maintained clean, tidy and safe work environment.

#### Ramp Service Agent, 02/2023 - Current Airport Terminal Services, Regina, SK

- Performance improvement
- Data Building and Modeling
- Analytical Thinking and Problem Solving
- Strong Interpersonal and Communication Skills
- Eagerness to Learn New Technologies
- Message Translation between Chinese and English

- Regina, SK S4W 0T2
- 1-306-515-4650
- shaobilly@gmail.com
- Personal Website

# WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/yunti ng-shao-2a5827207/
- https://www.artstation.com/svakbr is
- https://catssister.github.io/Spooke y-Ball-Robot

#### **SKILLS**

- Microsoft Office (Words, Excel and PowerPoint) - Mac & Windows
- Logical recruiting with critical, analytical and creative thinking ideologies
- Creative Suite: Photoshop,
   Premiere Pro, InDesign,
   illustration, Bridge, Lightroom,
   DaVinci Pro, Final Cut Pro, Affinity
   Series, Ableton Lite,C4D, Blender,
   Maya, SolidEdge
- Photography Taking by severe composition and framing consideration
- Photoshop Raw filter advanced user
- 3D modeling, post production & installation
- Voice production: recording, capturing, editing
- Creative Visualization & aesthetics
- Design and print modeling 3D printer user
- Eagerness to learn new Technologies
- Mandarin native speaker and fourteen years English speaker
- Strong interpersonal and Communication skills
- Food preparation and safety
- Active Listening

Deicing of aircraft

- Ethical Codes Adherence
- Microsoft Office, Communicated closely with ground crew, flight crew, and tow person via headset radio to maintain loading and unloading safety and efficiency
- Safely operated various types of equipment such as conveyor belts, push-back tractors and tugs
- Performed mathematical functions to interpret aircraft weight and balance loading instructions
- Loaded and unloaded luggage and freight and assisted crew and travelers with bags for over 10 daily flights
- Coordinated ground crew activities to complete objectives on schedule
- Cleaned airplanes between flights, sanitized lavatories and seat trays as per company specifications
- Operated equipment while observing standard safety procedures
- Verified quantity and description of materials received by checking merchandise against packing list
- Verified documentation and condition of freight to assure quality standards were achieved.

#### CSL Tax Professional, 02/2023 - 05/2023 H&R Block, Regina, SK

- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity
- Carried out day-day-day duties accurately and efficiently
- Demonstrated respect, friendliness and willingness to help wherever needed
- Worked flexible hours; night, weekend, and holiday shifts
- Performed duties in accordance with applicable standards, policies and regulatory guidelines to promote safe working environment
- Maintained energy and enthusiasm in fast-paced environment
- Offered friendly and efficient service to customers, handled challenging situations with ease
- Served customers and followed outlined steps of service.

### Radio Frequency Identification, 07/2022 - 11/2022 Regina Public Library, Regina, SK

- Quickly learn database organizing skills to speed up work efficiency
- Accurately and efficiently complete the record of daily book electronic ID
- Flexible working hours, weekend and night shift
- Be energetic and enthusiastic in a fast and efficient working environment
- Use critical thinking to solve problems in different ways
- Keep good attendance records and arrive at work on time
- It reflects a good technical level and has a good understanding of digital book management system
- Maintained energy and enthusiasm in fast-paced environment

- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions
- Actively listened to customers, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to supervisor.

#### Teaching Assistant, 01/2022 - 04/2022 University Of Regina, Regina, SK

- Support in-depth research on topics of the week
- Use visual aids and remote technical support to help professors teach
- Assist professors in the management and coordination of students' homework to ensure a positive learning environment
- Assisting the professor to enter the students' homework and exam scores through the online system
- Presented wide range of information to students using hands-on instructional techniques for effective comprehension
- Supported planning and preparation for culturally-diverse class sessions
- Worked with teachers to optimize learning plans based on student test grades and evaluations.

#### Distribution Clerk, 05/2018 - 08/2021 Great Asian Market, Regina, SK

- Documented stock records and schedules accurately
- Scheduled pickups and deliveries to maintain smooth operations
- Accelerated consumer purchasing habits by increasing distribution and availability across range of retail outlets
- Uncovered and resolved errors with minimal oversight
- Collaborated with other departments on supply and quality issues
- Managed and maintained warehouse to comply with company policies and federal regulations.

#### Food Deliverer, 04/2017 - 01/2021 Skip The Dishes, Regina, SK

- Completed on-time deliveries by choosing the best and most efficient routes
- Verified daily deliveries against shipping instructions before delivering to customers
- Kept detailed records of completed or in-progress deliveries using hand-held devices and camera images
- Created and submitted delivery and DOT logs
- Communicated regularly with the dispatcher for delivery route details and changes
- Processed payments, made changes and provided receipts
- Immediately addressed problems with customers to promote speedy resolution

### CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Food Safe, Saskatchewan Health Authority January 12, 2022
- Circular Economy For The Waste Sector In South Africa, United Nations Institute for Training and Research October 23, 2022
- An Introduction to Climate Change And Human Rights, United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change - October 23, 2022
- Storytelling For Impact In Your Classroom: Photography August 18, 2023
- Applying Geographic Thinking Skills with Your Learners August 18,2023
- The International Observe the Moon Night 2023 PARTICIPATION -August 21, 2023